Guide to the Rice University Information Files, 1910-2019 UA 361
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XVI: P
  - Papakonstantinou, Anne
  - Papoutsakis, E. Terry
  - Parades
  - Parents and Families
  - Parents Day/Weekend
  - Parents Guide
  - Parish, Alvis W.
  - Parish, John E.
  - Parish, Walter A.
  - Parker, Annise
  - Parker Jon Kimura
  - Parking
  - Parking 1992, Study of
  - Parks, Thomas W.
  - [Rice] Parliament
  - Parrish, Noel
  - Parry, Ronald J.
  - Parsons, David
  - Parsons, Frank A.
  - Parsons, Spencer
  - Pasley, Paul R.
  - Pasquali, Matteo
  - Passport to Houston
  - Pastoriza, Joseph J.
  - Pastrana, Andres
  - Patents
  - Patrick, Albert T.
    See also: Patrick Case (Oversized Material Section 8)
  - Patten, Robert L.
  - Patterson, Ronald
  - Patterson Sports Performance Center
  - Pattie, Frank A.
  - Paul Kennon Memorial Symposium
  - Payne, the Right Reverend Claude E.
  - PBX System
  - Pearson, James Boyd
  - Pecht, Lee
  - Peden, E.A. (Mr. and Mrs.)
  - Pei, I.M.
  - Pelli, Cesar
  - Pence, Mike
  - Pendleton, Ellen
  - [Rice] Pennant
  - Penrose, Roger
  - People's Republic of China Visit
  - Perez, Bernado
  - Perkins, Meg
  - Perkins, Sallie Shepherd
  - Perot, H. Ross
  - Perrine, Richard
  - Perry, Gov. Rick
  - Pershing, John J.
  - Persian Gulf Crisis
  - Personnel manuals
  - Personnel survey
  - Perzynska, Kinga
  - Perzynska, Kinga - Writings
  - Peterkin, George
  - Peters, C.J.
  - Peterson, Ann
  - Peterson, Bill
  - Pfeiffer, Paul Edwin
  - Pharr, George M.
  - Phi Lambda Upsilon
  - Phillips, Gerald Cleveland
  - Philosophy, Department of
  - Philpott, Charles
  - Physical Education, Department of
    see also: Scott, Harry A.
  - Physical Plant
  - Physics Building
  - Physics Colloquium
  - Physics, Department of
  - Physics and Astronomy News
  - Pi Delta Phi
    See also: Beauvoir, Simone De
  - Piazza, Enrico
  - Pickens, T. Boone
  - Picnics
  - Pinkerton's National Detective Agency, Inc.
  - Pinn, Anthony
  - Piper, William
  - Pisegna, Loretta
  - Pitman, Russell
  - Pittman, Blair
  - Pitzer, Jean M. (Mrs. Kenneth S.)
  - Pitzer, Kenneth S. (2 folders)
  - Pitzer, Kenneth S. - Inauguration
  - Pitzer, Kenneth S. - Resignation and Stanford U.
  - Pitzer, Kenneth S. - Resignation Newsclips
  - Pitzer, Kenneth S. - Rice Appointment
  - Planning and Construction, Office of
    See also: [Seeley G.] Mudd Computer Science Laboratory; Abercrombie Lab; Mechanical Engineering Building
  - [Rice Univ.] Planning Survey
  - Plapp, John E.
  - Playwright's Showcase
  - Poetry and Poetics Colloquium Committee
  - Poindexter, Hally Beth
  - Political Science, Department of
  - Politics
  - Polk, James Robert
  - Polking, J.C.
  - Pollak-Ottendorf, Emil
  - Pollard, Jack Critz
  - Pollard, William
  - Pomerantz, James R.
  - Pomerat, Roland
  - Population Symposium
  - Port Arthur Rice Club
  - Porter, Milton Brockett
  - Port of Houston
  - Port of Houston and Cotton Exchange, 1919-1965
  - Positions: East Asia Cultures Critique
  - [The] Posse Foundation
  - Post, Stephanie
  - Posthumous Degrees
  - Potter, David M.
  - Poulos, Basilios
  - Pound, Joseph H.
  - "Powderpuff" Women's Football (flag football)
  - Powell, Colin
  - Powell, John
  - Power Plant
  - POW'S - WWII
  - [Rice Native American] Pow-Wow
  - [Rice] Pranks
  - Prayer/Invocation at football games
  - [Rice] Pre-Law Association/Society
  - [Rice] Pre-Med Society
  - Presbyterian Student Assoc.
  - Preservation Week
  - [Rice] Presidential Inaugurations
  - [Rice] Presidential Search Committee
  - [U.S.] Presidents at Rice
  - President's Club
    See also: Rice University Fund (RUF)
  - President's Executive Luncheons
  - President's Graduate Fellowship Program
  - [Rice] President's House
    See also: MS 352, Watkin Papers, Box 3
  - President's Society of Rice University
  - [Rice] Press Club
  - Pride
    See also: Gay/Lesbian Support Group
  - [HRH] Prince Phillip - Visit to Rice '82
  - [Rice] Print Center
  - Printer's Marks
  - Print Making Studio
  - Printing Museum
  - Proctor, Office of
  - [Rice] Program Council
  - Property owned by Rice U.
  - [Student] Protests
    See also: Mackey, Louis; Kelly, Hugh Rice; Hoffman, Abbie
  - Provenzano, Foley S.
  - Psychiatric Services
  - Psychology Dept.
  - Pub
    See also: Willy's Pub
  - The Pub at Rice
    Students changed the name from Willy's Pub to The Pub at Rice in February 2022.
  - Public Affairs, [Rice] Division of
  - [Rice] Public Art Program
  - Publications - Campus
  - Publications Policy
  - Publications - Students
  - Publicity, General
  - [Houston] Public News
  - Pulley, Thomas E.
  - Putin, Vladimir
  - Putnam, Nicholas
- Series XVII: Q
  - Quality Enhancement Program
  - Quality Hill
  - Queer Resource Center
  - Queers and Allies
  - Queller, Dave
  - Questia
  - Quillen, Carol E.
  - Quin, Robert Pilcher
    See also: "R" Association
  - Quiocho, Florante
  - Quotations and Inscriptions
- Series XVIII: R
  - "R" & Quill Association
  - "R" Association Banquet
  - "R" Association - Newspaper Clippings
  - "R" Association - Programs
  - "R" Book
  - "R" Club Room
  - "R" Hall of Fame
  - "R2": Rice Review Literary Magazine
  - R & L Carriers New Orleans Bowl
  - R-STEM
  - Raaphorst, Madeleine
  - Rabin, Leah
  - Rabson, Thomas A.
  - Race/Rice: The State of Minority Students at Rice University
  - Rachleff, Larry
  - Racial Harassment
  - Racial Solidarity Week
  - Racing Owls
  - [Rice University] Radio
    See also: KTRU
  - Radioactivity
  - Radulescu, Eugen
  - Rafferty, Jack
  - Ragsdale, Lyn
  - Rally Club
  - RAMAS (Rice Association of Mexican-American Students)
    See also: HACER
  - Rambaud, Mrs. L.B. and Rice U. [will]
  - Rambin, J. Howard
  - Ramirez, Elias G.
  - Ramsey, Sir William
  - Randolph, Richard
  - Ransom, Harry S.
  - Rao, Sandhya
  - Rape
  - Rape Prevention
  - Raphael, Emanuel
  - Rath, R. John
  - Rathbone, Basil
  - Rather, John Thomas Jr.
  - Ravel, Maurice
    See also: EOL Office records; Lectures in Music 1922-1929
  - The Raven
  - Ray, Robert H.
  - Ray Taylor
  - Rayzor Chair of Philosophy
  - Rayzor Hall
  - Rayzor, Jesse Newton
  - Read, Clark
  - Reagan, Captain T. Mills
  - Reagan, Ronald
  - Real Estate
  - Reasoner, David L.
  - Reasoner, Harry
  - Rebounders Club
  - Reckling Park
  - Reckling, Thomas Radcliffe, III
  - Recknagel, Marsha
  - Recreation Center, Wellness and
  - Recruitment - Minorities
  - Recyclemania
  - Recycling Center
  - Red, David D.
  - Red, H. Lel
  - Redwine, Shirley
  - Reed, Kennard W., Jr.
  - Regional Information and Communication Exchange (R.I.C.E.)
  - Registrar, Office of the
  - Registration
    See also: Slimes and Slime Parade
  - Regulations Governing Student Organizations 1962 - 1965
  - Reid, H. Kittrell
  - Reiff, Patricia
  - Reiland, Pamela
  - Reinke, Edwin Eustace
  - Reiser, Adam
  - Relay Games
  - Religion
  - Religious Emphasis Week
  - Religious Pamphlets Distribution on Campus - Controversy
  - Religious Studies, Department of
    See also: Rutledge, David
  - Relocation Proposal
  - Remote Control Club
  - Renaissance Society of America
  - Renoir Foundation
  - Research at Rice - Externally Supported
  - Research @ Rice - monthly tipsheet
  - [Rice] Research Institutes
  - Research Sponsor Seminar
  - Residential College Expansion Plan
  - Residential College Information Systems (RCIS)
  - Residential College System (4 Folders)
    Contains information from Caleb McDaniel marking the change of Master to Magister.
  - Resinkoff, H.L.
  - Respert, Shawn
  - Retirement Plan
  - Reunions (not Homecoming)
  - Reynolds, F. Fisher
  - Reynolds, Dr. Luolin Storey Browning
  - Reynolds, Sally
  - Reynolds, Walter Moore
  - Rhodes, H.R. "Ike"
  - Rice African Student Association (RASA)
  - Rice Alliance for Mental Health Awareness (RAMHA)
  - Rice Alliance for Technology & Entrepreneurship
  - Rice Alumni Travel
  - Rice Ambassadors
  - Rice Art Program
  - Rice Associates (3 Folders)
  - Rice Associates Roundtable
  - Rice Aviation Field
  - Rice, Benjamin B.
  - Rice Board of Governors and Trustees
  - Rice Booster Club
  - Rice Broadcast Television
  - Rice Building Workshop
  - Rice Business Network
  - Rice Business Plan Competition
  - Rice Center for Community Design and Research
  - Rice Center for Cultural Studies
  - Rice Center for Education
  - Rice Center for Engineering Leadership
  - Rice Chamber Orchestra
  - Rice Cherry House
    See also: Nichols-Rice-Cherry House
  - Rice Children's Campus
  - Rice Chinese Student Association
  - Rice Christian Community
    See also: Religion
  - Rice, Condoleezza
  - Rice Counseling Center
  - Rice Cricket Club
  - Rice Cultivator
  - Rice Dance Troupe
  - Rice, David- Family
  - Rice Day before 1959
  - Rice Day, 1959
  - Rice Day, 1960
  - Rice Day, 2010-
  - Rice Daycare Center
  - Rice, Elizabeth Baldwin
  - Rice Emergency Medical Service (REMS)
  - Rice Engineering Day
  - Rice Engineering Design & Development Institute
  - Rice European Alliance
  - Rice Family Genealogies
  - Rice Family Genealogies- Related Surnames
  - Rice for Access
  - Rice for Life
  - Rice Forum
  - Rice, Frederick Allyn
    See also: Rice Family Genealogies; papers at Houston Metropolitan Research Center and Houston Public Library
  - Rice Gallery
  - Rice Global Engineering and Construction Forum
  - [Distinguished] Rice Graduates
    Also contact Alumni Affairs
  - Rice Graduate Student Symposium
  - Rice, H. Baldwin
  - Rice/HISD School
  - Rice Historical Review
  - Rice Historical Room
  - Rice, Homer
  - Rice Hotel & Old Capital Club
  - Rice Inline Skating Club
  - Rice Institute for Policy Analysis (RIPA) (2 folders)
  - Rice Institute Offices - Commercial Bank Bldg.
  - Rice Institute Offices - Esperson Bldg.
  - Rice Institute Offices - Heitmann Co.
  - Rice Institute Offices - Scanlav Bldg.
  - Rice Institute Pamphlet
  - Rice Institute/University - Brochures and General Info.
  - Rice Institute/University - Clippings, to 1940
  - Rice Institute/University - Clippings, 1940's
  - Rice Institute/University - Clippings, 1950's
  - Rice Institute/University - Clippings, 1960's
  - Rice Institute/University - Clippings, 1970's
  - Rice Institute/University - Clippings, 1980's
  - Rice Institute/University - Clippings, 1990's
  - Rice Institute/University - Clippings, 2000's
  - Rice International Internship Program
  - Rice Karate Club
  - Rice, Jonas Shearn
  - Rice Land & Vicinity
  - Rice Land Lumber Company
  - Rice Management Co.
  - Rice, Margaret Clara Bremond
  - Rice Memorial Arboretum
    See also: [Rice] Memorial Arboretum
  - Rice Model Science Lab (RML)
  - Rice/NASA Films
  - Rice News
  - Rice Nite
  - Rice [Campus] Observatory
  - Rice Outreach Mentoring Program (ROMP)
  - Rice Owl
  - Rice Owl Club
  - Rice - Pan American Observatory
  - Rice Peace Forum
  - Rice Philharmonics
  - Rice Players
  - Rice Program Council
  - Rice Program for Managers
  - Rice Publishing Program (2)
  - Rice Quantum Institute
  - Rice Quarterback Club
  - Rice Radio
  - Rice Red Cross Auxiliary
  - Rice Republicans
    See also: Young Republican Club
  - Rice Research News
  - Rice Rowers
  - Rice School (La Escuela Rice)
  - Rice School Writing Project
  - Rice Science Fiction and Fantasy Association
  - Rice Science Olympiad
  - [The] Rice Sentinel
  - Rice Sextant Club
  - Rice Space Institute
  - Rice Speak
  - Rice Sports Day
  - Rice Standard
  - Rice Student Volunteer Program (RSVP)
  - Rice Summer Business Institute
  - Rice Taiwanese Association (RTA)
  - Rice, Texas
  - Rice: The Next Century [Campaign] (2 folders)
  - Rice Theater Program
  - Rice Trial
  - Rice Trust Inc.
  - Rice TV
  - [The] Rice Undergraduate
  - Rice Undergraduate Observatory
  - Rice Undergraduate Research Society (RURS)
  - Rice University Business and Professional Women
  - Rice University Business Society
  - Rice University Fund (RUF)
  - Rice University Fund Council
  - Rice University - Museum Collaborative Partnership
  - Rice University Native American Student Association
  - Rice University Press
  - Rice University Review
  - Rice University School Math Project
  - [S.S.] Rice Victory
  - Rice Village
  - Rice Walk
  - Rice, William Marsh
  - Rice, William Marsh - Celebrations
  - Rice, William Marsh - Masonic Membership
  - Rice, William Marsh - Murder
  - Rice, William Marsh - Portraits
  - Rice, William Marsh - Published Articles about
  - Rice, William Marsh - Will
  - Rice, William Marsh, Jr.
  - Rice Women Conference & Rice Women's Conference
  - Rice Women in Computing
  - Rice Women's Alliance
  - Rice Women's Club
  - Rice Works
  - Rice-at-Large
  - RICEFEST
  - RiceInfo
  - Rich, M/M Hershel
  - Richards, Hugh
  - Richards-Kortum, Rebecca
  - Richardson, A. S.
  - Richardson, Sid Williams
  - Richmond, Art Forum
  - Richter, George Holmes
  - Ricker, Norman H.
  - Rickover, Hyman G.
  - Ride, Sally
  - Rienzi (Harris Masterson III's home)
  - [Rice] Rifle Team
  - Rigdon, Trish
  - Rimberg, Alexander
  - Rimlinger, Gaston
  - Rincon Oil Field
  - Ringe, Emilie
  - [Rice] Rings
  - Rinzler, Andrew
  - [Rice] Riot
  - [The] Rip-Off
    See also: Summer School for High School Students
  - Rixner, Scott
  - Ro, Tony
  - Robert, Marc
  - Roberts, Jabus
  - Roberts, John (U.S. Chief Justice)
  - Rockefeller Fellows
  - Rockefeller, Winthrop
  - Rodell, Elizabeth Goodson
  - Rodeo Exhibition 1928
  - Rodriguez, Peter
  - Roe, Herbert N.
  - Roediger, Henry L. III
  - Rogers, Chris
  - Rogers, John J.W.
  - Rogers, Karen Hess
  - Rojo, Javier
  - Role Models Program
  - Roll & Quill Society
  - Romeo
  - Romero Da Silva, Yvonne
  - Romney, Mitt
  - Rondelet, 1947-
    See also: May Fete Clippings
  - Rooke, David L.
  - Roos, Charles F.
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor
  - Roper, Daniel C.
  - Rorschach, Harold E.
  - Rose, Jasper
  - Ross, Alan
  - Ross, Marian Dean
  - Rosselini, Roberto
  - Rossini, Frederick D.
  - Rotary Club
  - ROTC
    See also: Naval ROTC
  - ROTC Rebellion 1918
  - Roth, Bert
  - Rothrock, Edward S.
  - Rouault, Georges
  - Rousseau-Raaphorst, Madeleine Marie Eugenie
  - Roux, Robert
  - Rowe, Peter G.
  - [Rice] Rowing Club
  - Rowley, Richard L.
  - Royal Society for the Encouragement of Arts, Manufactures and Commerce
  - Rozek Barbara
  - RTV5
  - Rubash, Joyce
  - Rubey, William W.
  - Rubin, Jerry
  - Rudee, Mervyn L.
  - Rudolph, Fred
  - Rudy, Ellis & Beverly
  - [Rice] Rugby team
  - Rundel, Robert D.
  - Rupp, George E.
  - Rupp, George E. - Inauguration
  - RUSP (Rice Undergraduate Scholars Program)
  - Russell Frank B.
  - Russell, George W (A.E.)
  - Rust, W.M.
  - Rutledge, David
  - Ryan, Frank B.
  - Ryba, Jane & Joan
  - Ryon Chair in Engineering
  - Ryon, Lewis B.
  - [Rice] Shooting Club
- Series XIX: S
  - Sachnowitz, Larry J.
  - Sadler, Mitchell, Sr.
  - [German-Texas] Saengerfest
  - SAFE Rice
  - Safety Bulletin
  - [Rice] Sailing Club
  - Saint Anne's Church
  - Saint Arnold Brewing Company
  - Salesmen's Club
  - [Nicolas] Salgo Distinguished Teaching Award
  - Salinas, Phillip
  - Sallyport
  - Sallyport Society
  - Salsburg, Zevi W.
  - Sam Houston Park
  - Sammy (Mascot)
  - Sammy Awards
  - Sammy Rocket Probes
  - Sammy's (Cafeteria)
  - Sampleton, George
  - Samurai (Club)
  - Sanborn, Bob
  - Sandall, Roger
  - Sanders, Elizabeth M.
  - Sanders, Floreine B.
  - Sanders, Gerry
  - Sanders, Isaac
  - Sanders, Paula
  - San Jacinto Battleground & Museum
  - Santos, Adele de Sousa
  - Santos, Antonio de Sousa
  - Sarah Lane Literary Society
    See also: Lane, Sarah
  - Sarofim, Fayez
  - SARS (severe acute respiratory syndrome)
  - Sass, Ronald L.
  - SATC
  - Savage, Catherine H.
  - Sawyer, Dale & Elise
  - Sayler, David
  - Scheid, Mark
  - Schell, Rick
  - Schill, Gus A., Jr.
  - Schirra, Walter M., Jr
  - Schlesinger, John
  - Schmider, Edward
  - Schmidt, Helmut
  - Schnee, Amanda M.
  - Schneider, David J.
  - Schneider, Elma
  - Schnoebelen, Anne
  - Scholarships and Fellowships, Office of
  - Scholarships - Cohn
  - Scholarships - Cooke
  - Scholarships - Fulbright
  - Scholarships, general (2 folders)
  - Scholarships - Golden Anniversaries
  - Scholarships - Goldwater
  - Scholarships - Marshall
  - Scholarships - Mitchell
  - Scholarships - Recruitment into Collegiate Education through Minority Scholarships (RICE-TMS)
  - Scholarships - Rhodes
  - Scholarships - Ripley
  - Scholarships - Rotary
  - Scholarships - Truman
  - Scholarships - Udall
  - Scholarships - Wagoner
  - "Scholarships at Work"
  - Schorre, Charles
  - Schroepfer, George J.
  - Schuberth, Richard E.
  - Schuler, Doug
  - Schuler, Mike
  - Schum, David
  - Schwarzkopf, Gen. H. Norman
  - Scott, David W.
  - Scott, Harry A.
  - Scott, John Frederik
  - Scott, John T.
  - Screwpull
  - Scrolls
    See also: Alumni Scrolls
  - Sculpture on Campus
  - SCUR (Southwest Center for Urban Research)
    See also: Urban Research, Southwest Center for
  - Scuseria, Gustavo
  - [Rice] Seal and Shield
    Seal adopted in 1918
  - Seale, Dorothy Weiser
  - Sears, Peter Gray
  - Security
  - Seed, Patricia
  - Seismograph
    See also: Space Science Department
  - Sellers, James
  - Semicentennial Celebration
  - Semicentennial Programs - Duplicates
  - Senior Follies
  - Senior Seminar in Foreign Policy
  - September 11, 2001
  - Seriff, Aaron J.
  - [Rice] Service Awards
    See also: Awards and Prizes
  - Sesquinet
  - Sewall, Blanche Harding
  - Sewall Hall
  - Sewall House
    See also: MS 431, B. H. Sewall Papers
  - Sexual Assault
  - Sexual Assault Awareness Week
  - Sexual Harassment
  - Shadowlawn
  - Shadyside
    See also: Cullinan; Wiess Residence
  - Shakespeare Festival
  - Shalen, Peter
  - Shamblin, L.S.
  - Shamoo, Yousif
  - Shamrock Bowl
  - Shanks, Rex, Jr.
  - Shaper, Sue Z.
  - Shaping Tomorrow
  - Shapiro, Beth
  - Shapiro, Eudice
  - [Rice] Shared Equipment Authority (SEA)
  - Sharp, Dudley
  - Sharp Lectureship/Lectures
  - Sharrar, Lee M.
  - Shatto, Gloria McDermith
  - Shaw, Robert
  - Shell Center for Sustainability
  - Shelton, Fred V.
  - Shelton, "Doctor" Jack
  - Shepard, Terry
  - Shepherd Chamber Players
  - Shepherd Foundation
  - Shepherd School of Music
  - Shepherd Singers
  - [The] Shepherd Society
  - Sher, George
  - Shetty, Anand
  - Shevardnadze, Eduard
  - Shibatani, Matt
  - Shimek, E. Joe
  - Shipley, Sir Arthur Everett
    See also: British Educational Mission
  - Shoah Foundation
  - Shoe Race
  - Shorts
    See also: Goode, W. J.
  - Shoss, Col. Morris L.
    Col. Shoss attended Rice 1933-1936. Alumni story request details his time in World War II.
  - Shumway, Nicolas
  - [Rice] Shuttle
  - SI & Susie Morris Lounge
  - SI Diamond Technology, inc.
  - Sibley, Marilyn M.
  - Sick, William
  - Sidewalk Superintendent, The
  - Sidis, William James
  - Sid Richardson College
    See also: Night of Innocence
  - Sid W. Richardson Foundation
  - Sigma Tau
  - Sigma Tau
  - Silberschlag, Eisig
  - Simons, Verne F.
  - Simpson, John D.
  - Sims, James R.
  - Skaaren, Warren
  - Skura, Meredith
  - Slaughter, John Willis
  - Slezak, Larry
  - Slimes and Slime parade
    See also: Registration
  - [Alfred P.] Sloan Foundation
  - Smalley, Richard (3 folders)
  - Smalley Institute
  - Smalley-Curl Institute
    See also: Smalley Institute, Rice Quantum Institute
  - Smith, Blakely
  - Smith, Brent
  - [Harry and Albert K.] Smith Chair in Architecture
  - Smith, George
  - Smith, Gordon
  - Smith, Harry K.
  - Smith, Ian
  - Smith, Kay
  - Smith, Lloyd
  - Smith, Richard J.
  - Smith, Roland B., Jr.
  - Smith, William D.
  - Snow, Edward
  - Sobel, Robert
  - Soccer
  - Social Sciences, School of
  - [Rice] Society of Automotive Engineers
  - [Rice] Society of Chemical Engineers
  - Society of Families
  - [Rice] Society of Mechanical Engineers
  - [Rice] Society of Petroleum Engineers
  - [Rice] Society of Physics Students
  - Sociology, Dept. of
  - Software Patent (Rice's 1st)
  - Sokol, Debbie
  - Solar Energy
  - Solar Power Research
  - Soligo, Ronald
  - Solutions Conference (Student Leaders Network)
  - [Rice] Songs/Yells
    This folder includes copies of the printed scores for Rice's Honor, Song of the Owls, the Rice Owl Fight Song, the Rice Hymn, and articles about Rice songs and traditions.
  - Sontag, Susan
  - Soo, Kim
  - Sorte, John
  - Sotheby's
  - South Asian Society
  - South Plant
  - South-Central Computational Science in Minority Institutions Consortium
  - Southampton (Neighborhood)
  - Southeast Medieval Association
  - Southern Regional Conference on Student Community Service
  - Southern University Conference
    see also: Accreditation
  - Southwest Athletic Conference
  - Southwest Conference
  - Southwest Conference Debate, 1984
  - Southwest Native Arts Festival
  - Southwest Research Institute
  - Southwestern Assembly
  - Soyinka, Wole
  - "Space City"
    See also: "Trasher"; [Rice] Thrasher
  - Space Physics and Astronomy, Department of
    See also: OWL Satellite; Space Science, Department of (Department of Space Science became Department of Space Physics and Astronomy in May 1973)
  - Space Program
  - Space Science, Department of
    See also: Aurora I; Balloon Launch; OWL Satelite; Seismograph; Space Physics and Astronomy, Department of
  - Space Science and Technology Building
  - Spanish Club
  - Spanish, Portuguese and Classics, Dept. of
  - Spanish Resource Center
  - Spanos, Pol D.
  - Speakers On Campus
  - Speakers Outreach Program
  - Spears, Monroe K.
  - Special Olympics
  - Specialist Club
  - Speleological Society
  - [Rice] Spelling Test
  - Spence, Dale
  - Sperandio, Christopher
  - Sponsored Research
  - Spontaneous Combustion (SpoCo)
  - Sports
  - Sports - Intramural
  - Sports Management Program
  - Sports, Spring, general
  - SPRAWL
  - Spring Theatre Festival
  - Spring Think
  - Spudis, Paul D.
  - Spuehler, Willy
  - Spuler, Rick
  - Squash Centre of the Southwest at Rice Univ.
  - Squire, Charles F.
  - SSPEED (Severe Storm Prediction, Education, and Evacuation from Disaster Center)
  - Staar, Richard F.
  - Stabell, Richard N.
  - Stadium (New)
  - Stadium (New) - Roof Proposal, 1966
  - Stadium (Old)
  - Stadium Proposal for Houston
  - [Rice] Staff Advisory Committee
  - [Rice] Staff Mentoring Program
  - "Staff News"
  - [Rice] Staff Wages
  - Stallman, Kurt
  - Stancliff, Fred J.
  - Stancliff, Mrs. Fred J.
  - Standish, William M.
  - Stanford, Geoffrey
  - Stark, Pauline
  - Statistics, Dept. of
  - Staub, John
  - Stebbings, Ronald
  - Steele, Henry
  - Steen, Frank
  - [Gertrude] Stein Bust
  - Stein, Joel
  - Stein, Robert
  - Step Ahead Program
  - Sterling, Robert R.
  - Stern, Isaac
  - Stevenson, Paul M.
  - Stevens, R. V.
  - Stewart, Charles
  - Stewart, Morris A.
  - Stirling, James
    Anderson Hall
  - Stockdale, James B.
  - Stokes, Gale
  - Stokowski, Leopold
  - Stoll, Richard
  - Stormer, John C.
  - Strait, George
  - Strange, Ray Watkin Hoagland
    See also: Hoagland, Ray Watkin
  - Strassman, Joan
  - Strategic Planning Committee/plans
  - Stratford, Sara P.
  - Straub, Steve
  - Strayer, Jenny
  - Streaking
  - Streete-Thompson, Kareem
  - Streets/Roads (Campus)
  - Stringham, Beth
  - Student Advising
  - Student Affairs
  - Student Affiliates of the American Chemical Society
  - Student's Army Training Corps
    See also: SATC
  - Student Association (SA)
  - Student Body Presidents' Conference
  - Student Center Proposal
  - Student Centered
  - Student Deaths
  - Student Handbook
  - Student Health Association
  - Student Health Insurance
  - Student Judicial Program
  - Student Life
  - Student Loans
  - Student Organizations
  - Student Physics Society
  - [Annual] Student Show
    See also: Fine Arts, Department of
  - Student Unrest
  - Student Volunteer Convention
  - Student-Faculty Art Show
  - Student-Faculty Dating
    See also: Sexual Harassment